bydeluxe.com 2017-06-09

# Deluxe Entertainment - Privacy Policy

### Effective Date of Current Policy: July 15, 2010

**Introduction**

This Privacy Policy describes the personally identifiable information that Deluxe Entertainment Services Group Inc. and its affiliates ("Deluxe," "we," "us," "our") collects through our website located at www.bydeluxe.com or any other Deluxe owned or operated website (the "Sites") and how we use that information. This Privacy Policy applies only to our online information-gathering and dissemination practices in connection with the Sites. It does not apply to any of our practices conducted offline.

**The Information We Collect**

Deluxe collects two types of information about the users of our Sites: 

1\. Personally identifiable information: In general, you do not have to provide your personally identifiable information to use our Sites. However, you may elect to electronically provide personally identifiable information such as your name, physical address, and email address to us through means described on the Sites from time to time. We use such personally identifiable information to respond to your inquiries. We may also use such personally identifiable information to notify you of events that we think may be of interest to you. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive notifications from us, please refer to the paragraph below captioned "Changing or Deleting Personal Information."

If you contact us by email through the Sites, we may keep a record of your contact information and correspondence. We reserve the right to use your email address and any information that you provide to us in your message to respond to you. In addition, on rare occasions, we may send by email important administrative information regarding either the Sites or services to users who have provided us with their email addresses. Because this information may be important to your use of the Sites, it is generally not possible to “opt out” of receiving these email communications. The Sites are not intended for or directed to children under eighteen (18) years of age, and Deluxe does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from such individuals. If you are younger than eighteen, do not provide any personally identifiable information while using the Sites.

2\. Non-personally identifiable information: we may use cookies to collect non-personally identifiable information in connection with the Sites. Our web pages may incorporate "pixel tags", "web beacons", or other similar tracking technologies (collectively, "pixel tags") that allow us or our agents to track the actions of users of our Sites. Pixel tags collect non-personally identifiable information, such as the identity of your internet service provider, the IP address of the computer you are using, the type of operating system and browser software that you use, the date and time of your access to our Sites, the website address, if any, from which you linked directly to our Sites, the website address, if any, to which you then travel from our Sites, and any similar traffic-related information. We may also aggregate your information with similar data collected from other users in order to help us improve our Sites and the services we provide through our Sites. We do not use this data in any way to create or maintain a personal profile of you or to collect personally identifiable information from you.

**How We Use the Information We Collect**

Generally, we will not disclose the personally identifiable information we collect through your use of the Sites to any unaffiliated third parties. However, we do reserve the right to provide such information to our affiliates and subsidiaries and with our and their employees, contractors, agents, and designees to the extent necessary to enable them to perform certain Site-related services (for example, web hosting, to improve Site-related services and features, or for maintenance services) on our behalf. We also reserve the right to disclose such information to any third party if we believe that we are required to do so for any or all of the following reasons: (i) by law; (ii) to comply with certain legal processes or governmental requests; (iii) to prevent, investigate, detect, or prosecute criminal offenses or attacks on the technical integrity of the Sites or our network; and/or (iv) to protect the rights, property, or safety of Deluxe and its affiliates, their partners, and employees, the users of the Sites, or the public.

**Changing or Deleting Personal Information**

If you would like to change your personal information, if you no longer wish to receive materials from us, or if want your personal information removed from Deluxe's database, please email the applicable Deluxe contact listed on the applicable Site. Alternatively, when you receive materials from us by email or other communications, you can make use of the "opt out" provision in such communications (or other "opt out" options that may be provided to you) so we know you no longer want to receive such materials from us.

**Security**

Deluxe seeks to adopt commercially reasonable security measures that are consistent with industry practice in order to assist with protection against the loss, misuse, and alteration of personally identifiable information that is under our control. Unfortunately, no security system or system of transmitting data over the Internet is guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result of the foregoing, while we do undertake commercially reasonable efforts to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee the security of our servers, the means by which information is transmitted between your computer and Deluxe's servers, or any information shared with us or with any third party through or in connection with the Sites. You provide all such information entirely AT YOUR OWN RISK.

**Revisions to Our Privacy Policy**

The Internet and its benefits are evolving rapidly, as are the ways people use the Internet and also the laws surrounding such use. Deluxe therefore reserves the right to update and revise this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time, as it deems necessary or appropriate. You may determine if this Privacy Policy has been revised since your last visit by referring to the "Effective Date of Current Policy" date noted at the top of this page. Your use of our Sites constitutes your acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy as amended or revised by us, and you should therefore review this Privacy Policy regularly in order to ensure your awareness of its terms.

**Business Transfers and Other Events**

Deluxe reserves the right to transfer any and all information that we collect from users, or that we otherwise collect in connection with the Sites, including, without limitation, to third parties, in the event of any liquidation or dissolution, or a sale or transfer of assets or of any portion of, our business.

**Links to Other Sites**

Our Sites may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not and cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of other websites and that this Privacy Policy applies only to the information that we collect through the Sites. Thus, we encourage you to read the privacy statements of all of the destination websites which you visit.
